<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fourth Conference on Computational Humanities Research on Computational Humanities Research 2023</title>
    <link>http://2023.computational-humanities-research/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fourth Conference on Computational Humanities Research on Computational Humanities Research 2023</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 11:12:14 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://2023.computational-humanities-research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Past Events</title>
      <link>http://2023.computational-humanities-research/archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 16:05:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://2023.computational-humanities-research/archive/</guid>
      <description>CHR2022 CHR2022 was a three-day conference held on December 12 to 14, 2022. The program committee and organizers accepted 29 papers, which have been published with CEUR-WS: https://ceur-ws.org/Vol-3290/. See https://2022.computational-humanities-research.org/ for more information about CHR2022.
CHR2021 CHR2021 was a three-day conference held on November 17 to 19, 2021. The program committee and organizers accepted 29 papers, which have been published with CEUR-WS: http://ceur-ws.org/Vol-2989/. See https://2021.computational-humanities-research.org/ for more information about CHR2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join the Community</title>
      <link>http://2023.computational-humanities-research/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 11:12:28 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://2023.computational-humanities-research/community/</guid>
      <description>We cordially invite you and other interested parties to join the Computational Humanities Research forum! The forum serves as an asynchronous platform to discuss all ideas and questions related to computational humanities research. These can be in-depth discussions about fundamental topics and questions of the discipline, or very practical ones, for example about how best to tackle a certain technical (coding) problem. And everything in between. Come join!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join the Community</title>
      <link>http://2023.computational-humanities-research/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 11:12:28 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://2023.computational-humanities-research/contact/</guid>
      <description>Community Please join our Computational Humanities Research forum! The forum serves as an asynchronous platform to discuss all ideas and questions related to computational humanities research. These can be in-depth discussions about fundamental topics and questions of the discipline, or very practical ones, for example about how best to tackle a certain technical (coding) problem. And everything in between. Come join!
Contact For questions, ideas, or support, contact the organizers or drop us a line on the forum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call for Papers</title>
      <link>http://2023.computational-humanities-research/cfp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 11:11:58 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://2023.computational-humanities-research/cfp/</guid>
      <description>Registration is now open In the arts and humanities, the use of computational, statistical, and mathematical approaches has considerably increased in recent years. This research is characterized by the use of formal methods and the construction of explicit, computational models. This includes quantitative, statistical approaches, but also more generally computational methods for processing and analyzing data, as well as theoretical reflections on these approaches. Despite the undeniable growth of this research area, many scholars still struggle to find suitable research-oriented venues to present and publish computational work that does not lose sight of traditional modes of inquiry in the arts and humanities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Venue</title>
      <link>http://2023.computational-humanities-research/venue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 11:11:58 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://2023.computational-humanities-research/venue/</guid>
      <description>The conference will be held at EPITA (L&amp;rsquo;École pour l’informatique et les techniques avancées) on 14-16 Rue Voltaire, 94270 Le Kremlin-Bicêtre
To orient yourself at any time, a map of the school is available online at the following address. https://epimap.fr/kb Just type the name of any room to find it.
The conference will take place across several rooms:
 Amphi 3 (plenary sessions) KB 403 (conference room) KB 404 (conference room) Amphi 0 (for coffee breaks and cocktail)  You can access the site via subway (Line 7 - “Porte d’Italie”), tram (Line 3a - “Porte d’Italie”) or bus (Line 47 - “Roger Salengro - Fontainebleau”).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://2023.computational-humanities-research/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://2023.computational-humanities-research/people/</guid>
      <description>Programme Chairs  Fotis Jannidis, University of Würzburg Iza Romanowska, Aarhus University Artjoms Šeļa, Institute of Polish Language, Polish Academy of Sciences  Organizers  Florian Cafiero, Institut d&amp;rsquo;Etudes Politiques de Paris / École nationale des chartes Fotis Jannidis, University of Würzburg Folgert Karsdorp, KNAW Meertens Institute Marie Puren, EPITA / Centre Jean Mabillon - École nationale des chartes Iza Romanowska, Aarhus University Artjoms Šeļa, Institute of Polish Language (Polish Academy of Sciences) Melvin Wevers, University of Amsterdam  Programme Committee Adela Sobotkova, Aarhus University</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHR2023 Programme</title>
      <link>http://2023.computational-humanities-research/programme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://2023.computational-humanities-research/programme/</guid>
      <description>Please note that all times are in Central European Time (CET)
Wednesday, December 6, 2023 (Day 1)  09:00-10:30: Workshops, registration 10:30-11:15: Coffee break, registration 11:15-11:30: CHR opening words 11:30-13:00: Session 1: Historical change. Chair: Artjoms Šeļa 13:00-14:30: Lunch 14:30-16:00: Session 2A: Language. Chair: Kristoffer Nielbo ////// Session 2B: History. Chair: Sarah Lang 16:00-16:30: Coffee break 16:30-18:00: Keynote Richard McElreath (MPI for Evolutionary Anthropology). The importance of analog thinking for digital scholarship.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
